Hello, and welcome to a tutorial.
You can tell it is a tutorial because I am using the "tutorial voice".
If I spoke like this to people in real life, everyone would think I'm an asshole.
How to land on the Mun.
Well first, we need to build our ship.
We take this one and put it here!
Then, maybe we'll take this one and put it here.
Eventually, you will end up with an F-22 Raptor.
But it can't even leave the atmosphere!
...Let's try another fighter jet.
This one still can't leave the planet, so either planes built exclusively for combat aren't meant to reach the Mun, or...
more likely, just like in real life, it's not actually possible to travel to the Moon, you sheep!
My neighbour explained perfectly to me, and he is one of Europe's top physicists.
Well, at least according to himself.
He also doesn't believe in dolphins, but that's not physics.
So now the Kerbal higher-ups want us to fake a Mun landing,
so I started building a film studio, one thing led to another, and I landed on the Mun.
*sighs*
But the government is expecting us to fake it, so now we have to cover-up our failed cover-up for the cover-uppers,
AKA the government.
But how do we do that?
Hmm...
Nah, it's impossible.
They have to go.
So, we'll make a spacecraft that looks like an aeroplane,
then we'll make them think they're going to the Bahamas, but they are actually going to the Sun.
And their families can't sue us because the invitation only said "some place warm".
But killing off the entire government has created a power vacuum.
Some high-ranking government officials should seriously take control of the situation.
Someone like the guy in charge of the space program!
But before I could fully tame the country, a civil war broke out.
But we don't have anything to fight them with...
Wait a minute!
We could take those fighter jets we created earlier!
It's almost like that was the plan all along!
To win a civil war, my biggest tip is to be ruthless.
A good rebel is a dead rebel.
But if we capture anyone, we won't have a public execution.
But nothing too gruesome, because we want to keep them family friendly.
Now, let's go win a war!
[dramatic music plays]
And with all the rebels dead or captured, we have full control of our Kerbals.
I'm probably going to rule it with an iron fist, probably with some radical ideology.
My dynasty shall rule for hundreds of years, and there's literally nothing that can stop us.
[gunshot noises]
[cheerful music plays]